Andrew Hardemon

Flagstaff, AZ 86001 | Phone: 404-937-0995 | Email: andrewhardemon@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrew-hardemon/ | GitHub: https://github.com/AeroAtlas My Portfolio: https://official-portfolio-atlas.herokuapp.com/

Summary

Senior Tutor and Teacher's Assistant for Full Stack Web Development with certification from the University of Arizona, previous managerial experience, and a passion for programming. Good at Communication, Collaboration, and Problem Solving. Was promoted to Senior tutor in under a month at Trilogy Education, and studied Java and Scala at EKU.

Technical Skills

Languages/Frameworks: JavaScript, Typescript, Java, Scala, React, Node.js, Express, SQL, MongoDB, CSS/HTML Other: Git, Bash, Linux, Heroku, Firebase, Agile, Scrum, RESTful APIs, TDD, Redux, MERN, Bootstrap, GraphQL

Projects

Safe For Work: project-sfw.herokuapp.com/ || github.com/Azorse/Project-SFW

- A program to track the knowledge retention of users using gamification techniques for lessons and quizzes
 - o Role: Create wireframe, React pages, general functionality, JavaScript, UI/UX
 - o Languages: React.js, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Bootstrap/CSS

Semi-Random Recommendations: project2beta.herokuapp.com/ || github.com/AeroAtlas/Project2Beta

- Web App with register/login that lets you find a random game or movie with certain parameters
 - Role: JavaScript, AJAX, API, main functionality, Front-End to Back-End connection
 - o Languages: Node.js, Handlebars, SQL, JavaScript, Bootstrap/CSS

Vamp-Desktop: https://vamp-desktop.herokuapp.com/ | https://github.com/AeroAtlas/vamp-desktop

React based Chat Application with image upload and automatic updating using socket-io
Role: Solo Project - *In Progress*. (Front-End, Back-End, Functionality, UI/UX, Design, Assets)
Languages: React, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, socket-io

Experience

Senior Tutor and Teacher's Assistant for Trilogy Education - 2020 - Present - (Online)

- Coach and Teach students in an online Full-stack Web Development course (MERN)
- Showcased my abilities as a student of Trilogy and was recommended by my teacher for the TA position.
- Also became a Tutor after 3 months and then Senior Tutor in under 1 month

Assistant Manager for Domino's Pizza, Inc - 2016-2018, 2019-Present (GA, KY, AZ)

- Directed employees, supervised work activity, ordered inventory, and managed labor and food cost.
- Earned a General Manager in Training position while at Domino's in Suwanee, GA.

Education

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development: University of Arizona, Phoenix, AZ, 2019-2020 An intense 24-week program for learning for the ins and outs of Full-Stack Web Development. Learning everything from JavaScript, CSS, and HTML to React, MongoDB, and SQL. Includes both Front-End and Back-End Web Development.